Finding Aid for Topographic Quadrangle Maps, 1895-[ongoing].
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:24,000
  - Shields - Yuma
    - Yuma 44085C7
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Described above (Folder 1)
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:25,000
  - Alanson-Frankfort (Folder 1:25,000 A-F)
    - Alanson 45084D7
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Alden 44085H3
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Bay Shore 45085C1
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Benzonia 44086E1
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Beulah 44086F1
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Buckley 44085E6
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Burdickville 44085G8
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Cadillac North 44085C4
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Cadillac South 44085B4
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Carp River 46089G7
      [covers 7.5x15 minute area]
      - Survey 1977; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Charlevoix 45085C3
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Clare 43084G7
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Dighton 44085A3
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Dinca 44085C1
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Elberta 44086E2
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Empire 44083H1
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Epsilon 45084C7
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Evart 43085H3
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Falmouth 44085B1
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Forest Beach 45085D1
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Frankfort 44086F2
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
  - Gills Pier-Lucas (Folder 1:25,000 G-L)
    - Gills Pier 45085A6
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Glen Arbor 44085H8
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Glen Haven 44086H1
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Good Harbor Bay 44085H7
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Grawn 44085F6
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Green Hills 46087C6
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1991, green overprint
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1992, green overprint
    - Harbor Springs 45084D8
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Hatton 43084H7
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Hersey 43085G4
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Hiram Point 45086G4
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1987, green overprint
    - Houghton Lake 44084C7
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Ironton 45085C2
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Jennings 44085C3
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Karlin 44085E7
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Kingsley 44085E5
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Lake Ann 44085F7
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Lake City 44085C2
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Lake George 43084H8
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Lake NE 43085H1
      - Survey 1981; print 1984; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Le Roy 44085A4
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Leland 45085A7
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Lucas 44085B3
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
  - Manton-Woods
    - Manton 44085D4 (Folder 1:25,000 M-Z)
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Maple City 44085G7
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Mapleton 44085H5
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Marion 44085A2
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Mayfield 44085F5
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Mc Bain 44085B2
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Merritt 44084C8
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Morey 44085D2
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - North Manitou Island 45085A8
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Northport 45085B5
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Northport NW 45085B6
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Omena 45085A5
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Petoskey 45084C8
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Platte River 44085F8
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Slaybaugh Corner 43085H4
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - South Manitou Island 45086A1
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Stittsville 44085D1
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Suttons Bay 44085H6
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Temple 44085A1
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Thompsonville 44085E8
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Traverse City SE 44085G5
      - Survey 1979; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Traverse City SW 44085G6
      - Survey 1980; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Williamsburg 44085G4
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Woods 43084G8
      - Survey 1981; print 1983; reprint 1984, green overprint
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:31,680
  - Ahmeek-Custer
    - Ahmeek 47088C4 (Folder Ahmeek-Custer)
      - Survey 1938, green overprint
    - Baldwin NW 43085H8
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Baldwin SE & SW 43085G7/G8
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Bark River SE 45087E3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Beaver Tail Point NE & NW 45084H1/H2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Bruneau Creek 47088C2
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Burnt Bluff NE 45086F5
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Burnt Bluff SW 45086E6
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Central 47088D2
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Chase NE 43085H5
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Chase NW 43085H6
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Chase SE & SW 43085G5/G6
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Cooks NE 45086H3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Cooks NW 45086H4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Cooks SW 45086G4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Crystal Falls 46088A3
      - Survey 1944 print 1946, green overprint
    - Custer NE 43086H1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Custer NW 43086H2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Custer SE 43086G1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Custer SW 43086G2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
  - Deer Lake-Gladstone
    - Deer Lake 47088C1 (Folder Deer Lake-Gladstone)
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Delaware 47088D1
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Driggs Lake NE 46086D1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Driggs Lake NW 46086D2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Driggs Lake SE 46086C1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Driggs Lake SW 46086C2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Epoufette SW 46085A2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Fort Wilkins 47087D7
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Fortune Lakes 46088A4
      - Survey 1944 print 1946, green overprint
    - Freesoil NW & NE 44086B1/B2
      - Survey 1931, 1933, green overprint
    - Freesoil SE 44086A1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Gaastra 46088A5
      - Survey 1944 print 1946, green overprint
    - Garden NE 45086H5
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Garden NW & SW 45086G6/H6
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Garden SE 45086G5
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Gay 47088B2
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Gibbs City 46088B6
      - Survey 1945 print 1946
    - Gilchrist NE 46085B3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Gilchrist NW 46085B4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Gilchrist SW 46085A4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Gladstone NE 45087H1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Gladstone NW 45087H2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Gladstone SE 45087G1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Gladstone SW 45087G2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
  - Gould City-Manistee
    - Gould City NE 46085B5 (Folder Gould City-Manistee)
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Gould City NW 46085B6
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Gould City SE 46085A5
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Gould City SW including Point Patterson NW 46085A6/45085H6
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Hart NE 43086F3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Hart NW 43086F4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Hart SE 43086E3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Hart SW 43086E4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Harvey NE 46087D3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Harvey NW 46087D4
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Harvey SE 46087C3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Harvey SW 46087C4
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Iron River 46088A6
      - Survey 1944 print 1946, green overprint
    - Lake Medora 47087D8
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Ludington NE 43086H3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Ludington NW 43086H4
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Ludington SE 43086G3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Ludington SW 43086G4
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Manistee NE and NW 44086B3/B4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Manistee SE 44086A3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Manistee SW 44086A4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
  - Manistique-Seul Choix Point (Folder Manistique-Seul Choix Point)
    - Manistique 45086H1/H2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Manistique River NE 46086B1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Manistique River NW 46086B2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Manistique River SE 46086A1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Manitou Island 47087D5
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Mohawk 47088C3
      - Survey 1938, green overprint
    - Moran NE 45084H7
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Moran NW 45084H8
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - New Haven 42082F7
      - Survey 1936, green overprint
    - Peninsula Point NE & NW 45086F7/F8
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Phoenix 47088D3
      - Survey 1938 print 1940, green overprint
    - Point Isabelle 47087C8
      - Survey 1938, green overprint
    - [Point Patterson NW 45085H6 Included in Gould City SW]
    - Point Place 41083F4
      - Survey 1934 print 1938, green overprint
    - Rapid River NE 45086H7
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Rapid River NW 45086H8
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Rapid River SE 45086G7
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Rapid River SW 45086G8
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Reno Beach 41083F3
      - Survey 1934 print 1938
    - Rock NE 46087B1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Rock NW 46087B2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Rock SE 46087A1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Rock SW 46087A2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Selfridge Field 42082E7
      - Survey 1936, green overprint
    - Seul Choix Point NE 45085H7
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Seul Choix Point NW 45085H8
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
  - Shingleton-Sylvania
    - Shingleton NE 46086D3 (Folder Shingleton-Sylvania)
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Shingleton SE 46086C3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Shingleton SW 46086C4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Skandia NE 46087D1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Skandia NW 46087D2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Skandia SE 46087C1
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Skandia SW 46087C2
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Skeels Lake NW & SE 46086A6/B6
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Skeels Lake SE 46086A5
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - St. Ignace NE 45084H5
      - Survey 1931, 1932, green overprint
    - St. Ignace NW 45084H6
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - St. Ignace-Moran South 45084G6/G7
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Steuben NE 46086B3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Steuben NW 46086B4
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Steuben SE 46086A3
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Sunset Lake 46088B5
      - Survey 1945 print 1946
    - Sylvania 41083F6
      - Survey 1934 print 1937, green overprint
  - Trenary-Whitney
    - Trenary NE & NW 46086B7/B8 (Folder Trenary-Whitney)
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Trenary SE 46086A7
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Trenary SW 46086A8
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Uno NE 46086B5
      - Survey 1931 (one copy stamped Skeels Lake NE), green overprint
    - Waldenburg 42082F8
      - Survey 1936, green overprint
    - Walkerville NE 43086F1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Walkerville NW 43086F2
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Walkerville SE 43086E1
      - Survey 1931, green overprint
    - Whitney NE 45087H3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
    - Whitney SE 45087G3
      - Survey 1932, green overprint
- Specials
  - Ann Arbor, Scale 1:63360 N4200-N4300/W8330-W8400 (Folder Specials)
    - Survey 1902; includes green vegetation overprint
      [Located in outsize folder]
  - Ann Arbor, Scale 1:125000 N4200-N4300/W8330-W8400
    - Survey 1902; print1904
    - Survey 1902; print 1904; reprint 1907
      [Found only in Ann Arbor folio, MH/4/W319/1908/R963]
    - Survey 1902; print 1904; reprint 1908
    - Survey 1902; print 1904; reprint 1914
      [Found only in Ann Arbor folio, MH/4/W319/1915/R963]
  - Calumet, Scale 1:62500 N4709-N4722/W8818-W8837
    - Survey 1909; print 1911
    - Survey 1909; print 1911; reprint 1925
  - Camp Custer, Scale 1:62500 N4215-N4230/W8500-W8530
    - Survey 1917; print 1918
  - Fletcher, Scale 1:20000 N4435-N4439/W8447-W8455
    - Survey 1928
  - Marquette, Scale 1:24000 N4630-N4640/W8720-W8730
    - Survey 1905
  - Menominee, Scale 1:62500 N4545-N4555/W8745-W8808
    [Also found in Menominee special folio, MH/3/M5/U58/1900]
    - Survey 1898; print 1900
    - Survey 1898; print 1901; reprint 1926
      [Title changed to Menominee Iron Range]
- Index Maps
  - September 1908 (Folder Indexes)
  - November 1928
  - March 1958
  - November 1958
  - August 1961
  - December 1964
  - July 1967
  - July 1969
  - November 1976
  - February 1978
  - January 1980
  - Index to topographic and other map coverage 1984
    [booklet]
  - Catalog of topographic and other published maps 1988